Hey, just a reminder that it actually is about race.
What's about race?
Everything.
Everything in America is about race.
And that's on purpose.
Legislation, school resource differences, it's all about race.
Medical care, crime, it's all about race.
All of it.
So when people try and tell you like, it's not about race, it is.
And so I wanted to come here today just to remind you that it is all about race.
And that until you actually realize that, it is never going to change.
It's not going to change by pretending it's not about race.
It's not going to pretend by acting like race doesn't exist.
It's never going to change because it is about race.
It is.
This is a nation that have people drinking from different water fountains because of the color of their skin.
It's about race.
It's not going to change because there's black Republicans.
It's not going to change because there's black cops.
It's not going to change because there's black housewives of wherever.
Like, it's just not.
Like, slavery happened.
It's about race.
And things did not change until everybody, or at least the majority of people, got on the same page and was like, hola, race!
Easy way to put it is that this country was built by white people who made their money by othering people.
It's a capitalist country.
So in order to keep that money, they feel like they got to keep othering people.
So get on the good foot.
Ba-dum-bum!